coaches how do you price your coaching
so that you can make sure that you both
feel confident when you're selling it
and that people will actually buy it
I've been helping coaches for The Last
21 years scale their businesses and I
want to show you the best way to
confidently price your business so that
people actually buy it from you so that
you feel good about it and people love
it for those of you that I haven't met
yet my name is Jeremiah Kowski and for
the last 21 years I've been building
coaching and course businesses in the
online space back then were CD and DVD
products and built multiple businesses
over the $10 million year mark and I
want to help you reach your goals with
your coaching and course business now
pricing is an area where a lot of people
there's a lot of different information
out there but one of the things you got
to do is you have to
detach your selfworth from what you're
charging and you need to start charging
for the result that you deliver now you
might be saying I'm a life coach I'm a
spiritual coach how do I do that that's
easy for you Jeremiah you sell an Roi
stuff like that let me explain
okay if you can take the experience the
transformation that you bring in
people's lives and then you extrapolate
it out what that means is you take the
timeline here's today and then here's
where they are next week and then where
are they next year and then where are
they at two years from now when you
extend that out you can see that the one
transformation of working with you
produced a ripple effect in their life
of results I remember my first Mentor
that I ever met changed my family's
future in fact it generated hundreds of
millions of dollars in potential profits
sadly number of different situations
things like that didn't produce that
much but it did generate close to $100
million over the years for my mom as
well as combined with myself and my
business as well as the ripple effect of
the lives that we've impacted during
that time
and so all of that to say this one
Mentor which then we met another mentor
and another mentor and by the way I
believe in people having mentors for
Seasons not like One Mentor forever but
I do find a lot of the clients that work
with me they stay for a while and I work
with them long term to help them get
results all that to say that if you are
a coach or Mentor that you got to look
at what is the long-term value of some
working with you what is the return on
investment that they're going to get and
and think about this too what is the
cost of in action that they can lose by
not working with you I'll tell you this
people who don't work with me the
economy inflation starts to go up I have
people who literally have been saying oh
yeah Jeremiah I'll work with you I'll
work with you eventually eventually
eventually they've been saying it for
four years and they are not in a better
position today by making excuses I have
other clients that are
literally have like gone from zero when
I started working with them 5 years ago
and today they're over the $10 million a
year mark in their business so it's like
that's the that's literally the cost of
inaction when somebody hears me and I
teach and they don't do anything with
what I'm saying and and it's and that
I'm I'm going to level with you is true
it's 100% true is that if you do listen
and apply if you subscribe to my YouTube
channel and you watch the different
content that I have if you watch the
different trainings that I have and
you're able to join my coaching program
you'll get results if you apply the
information if you start to do it and
that's what I'd love to help you with as
well the biggest area I find that a lot
of people get stuck in is understanding
their value so the other thing we got to
think about is
this is that pricing is a form of
boundaries as coaches we need to have
boundaries we want want people to use us
for their benefit you know I like I
desire for you to use me and my
information to make a ton of money that
would be the wisest thing that you could
do excuse me a little bit of a cough
here
but I cannot
attach the need for you to use what I'm
going to do
to my selfworth and how much I'm going
to price things to where I make it so
cheap that you don't do
anything
because I am just wanting to make sure
that you you work with me at all C like
I I used to be this way coaches get we
get desperate we want people to work
with us we want people to become our
clients we want people to use what we
teach that we end up undercutting
underpricing ourselves just to get a
client as far as that goes I was guilty
of this for years now I refuse to
there's a bare minimum cost of working
with me you got I got my free content
that's out there for the people who
can't afford it and and the ones who
know that they are supposed to work with
me to get the results they jump in and
they become a client we have an
incredible time together producing
results like my client Kim when she came
in and was able to make six figures with
her real estate offer in a down Market
or like Ian who was able to make over
$40,000 a month in his business after
applying this information when I met him
he was like I don't know how to make
this work I don't know if I could make
this work and I'm like no literally you
just do this stuff and it works and so
when you price your business you got to
establish yourself as an
authority the value that of how you see
yourself is the way that others will see
you and so people won't respect you or
your time or your value if you don't
respect you your time or your value and
you got to start seeing yourself as far
more valuable internally it starts with
the self-belief it starts with the
mindset it starts with seeing your value
as greater than just people using you
for their benefit but rather that you
are worth people paying a significant
amount for now on the return on
investment side of things pricing
yourself in at about 5 to
10% of whatever that return on
investment is generally I like to do
about 10% most of the clients who come
in and work with me the minimum
potential that they'll end up making is
about 20 to $40,000 a month in their
business will help them get to their
first 10,000 a lot of people actually
shoot right past that and make about
$220,000 a month consistently not just
one time but consistently in their
business when they start to do the work
when they start to apply
it and so if I price my program at 10%
of that it comes in right around
$2,000 as far as that goes and and and
again that's not per month but I'm
that's like a one-time fee as far as
that goes and that's very affordable
that's very doable for people we have
payment plans on that as well that
people can do $200 a month we have free
trials that people can take 14-day test
drive to try it out we give you free
courses just for trying it out it's a
it's an incredible deal honestly most
coaches don't offer that much but I
believe in our system so much that I
know that it gets people results that if
they can get in there and they can get
immersed in what we're doing they will
see the difference that it makes by
working with the best program that's out
there and I believe we have what like
not just one of the best programs but
that we have literally in like the top
tier of best programs and we've had
people that have been in multiple
coaching programs they've spent 10 times
what we charge for our program and they
tell me consistently Jeremiah your
program is better than those ones that I
spent 10 times as much for I hear this
all the time I'm not saying this to brag
but I'm saying this that when you can
create something of value you can start
to feel confident in what you price it
for and you can actually decide what
type of client that you want to work
with I love working with the person that
is at the place where you are where
you're trying to figure out your pricing
where you're trying to figure out how do
I want to package things how do I want
to put these things together and then
how do I start marketing these things
and how do I then start actually getting
clients and doing so in a 30 to 60 day
time period not a lot of time not a lot
lot of time spent Dilly dallying around
or wasting time but actually taking
action and getting results and that's
the kind of things that we see with our
clients when they go through our program
so when you Pro when you price your
program out you want to think about a
who is the type of person that I want to
attract to
me and your messaging also does
correlate to this pricing if you're
charging 10,000 20,000 $30,000 that's a
higher level of person who's looking for
a higher level of result they're looking
for at least 10 times 20 times that
result they're looking to make when they
work with me at least 200 to 500 to a
million dollars when they pay for a
higher level like that I have a
$119,000 one-on-one program that people
can work with me in and and in that
$199,000 program that's exactly the
investment that people make to be able
to get that oneon-one immediate access
on the things that they're looking for
and so we got these two tiers that I
offer that's what I I say a lot of
people have two
tiers have your one-on-one offering
being the highest level being something
that people can work for offer a payment
plan on that $119,000 can come out right
about $1600 a month which for a lot of
people is actually decently affordable
for most people when they're really
looking to produce a result $1,600 a
month is a great price point I think to
reach people as far as that goes okay
and then you know $200 to $300 a month
for something that's really delivering
value in a group setting one onone group
setting and then what you can do with
this is you can generate a real business
that's
making 300 400 $500,000 a year without
having to work more than 10 to 15 hours
a week that's the kind of business that
we've been able to build for ourselves
we were able to build a seven figure
business that's over a million dollars
in working just 10 to 15 hours a week by
positioning ourselves the right way by
creating the right type of content that
attracts the right people to us that
connects with the right kind of people
and that allows us to
truly reach the people that we're meant
to work
with and serve them at a very high level
and and we have the lowest amount of
chargebacks comp like no complaints from
people people absolutely love
it and it's because we've positioned it
in the right way we've made sure that
our messaging is aligned in the right
way and we priced it in a way where
we're not the cheapest option listen
don't be the cheapest option you don't
want to be the cheapy person that's out
there you want to be the one that you
know you're worth and you can feel very
confident about what you're pricing it
in at I recommend for a lot of people if
you're Marketing Online no less than
$500 for what you're offering and if you
do a payment plan on that you know you
could do a six payments of 97 bucks
super affordable for people as far as
that goes you could even offer a 12 pay
of $47 as far as that goes again it's a
little bit more expensive on the payment
plan they you can they can save a
hundred bucks $500 if they don't do
payments I've known a lot of people
they've actually generated I have a
client right now who's does about $60 to
$80,000 per
month and he just sells a a course every
6 weeks for $500 that's it or does a
three pay option on it for about hund I
think like $200 a payment is what it is
for three
payments and and he's making that much
consistently a month in his business
they he spends right around maybe 10,000
on ads and generates about 50,000 in in
in profit on the low end in his business
cash received by doing this by following
this model by pricing things at that
level if you're if you're cheaper than
and I want to talk about the different
levels of pricing if you're cheaper than
$97 I consider that just to be a sales
and marketing um tool it's not something
that delivers transformation it's
something that provides value but it's
not going to be the whole system like
for instance this video right here I I
know that I'm providing tremendous value
in this video already you've watched
this and if I've left some value for you
let me know in the comments below I'd
love to see that just to encourage
people it also helps the algorithm boost
some of these different videos if you if
you share in the comments like that
would love that would would appreciate
it any questions you have for me please
share that as far as that goes too but
in
this that when we give value there's a
difference between like a a free piece
of content like this and my whole
coaching program I have discovered what
are the Strategic messages that people
want and they're looking for in my free
content that I deliver and then what do
I actually charge for we've actually
surveyed people I have a document that
has nearly 200 pages on it 200 Pages
just of surveys of people that we've
worked with over the last two years of
what are they looking for and pricing
comes up all the time on that and so
that's an initial question that people
always ask me when working with me so
what I do is I I if something's priced
under
$97 I'm going to deliver value on these
entrylevel questions and concerns and
issues that people have as they're
coming through the door then what ends
up happening is is I have a group of
people when they come into my coaching
program they start to discover certain
areas where they're struggling with and
I don't teach on that stuff as much
outside of my coaching program like I'm
actually I'm actually starting to shift
my coaching program to even adjust for
where I'm seeing the most transformation
delivered with my clients which was
completely different than what I
expected for years um I found that if I
actually give the strategies away for
free that people often are coming to me
to figure out how to actually implement
it and really work through what are
those blocks that are stopping them from
implementing because they know the
strategies I give a lot of them away for
free if you're looking for the strategy
it's not rocket science I walk you
through it in my coaching program as
well very simple very easy to follow we
show you how to find the right prospects
how to promote your business in the
right way and then how to the most
important part close sales which is why
it produces so much revenue and cash
flow for our clients and then what are
the things that you run into along the
way the pitfalls so that I can be the
one to help guide and direct you and and
help move you past some of the different
hurdles and struggles that you might
have along the way and that's exactly
what what I work with people with every
single week in our
programs and so in that that's where
people make that investment with me but
if I'm charging under $97 and by the way
one of my favorite price points to do $7
$17 $27 just depends on how much value
is delivered but I love stuff for like
$7 to $17 because it's so cheap that
almost anybody's going to say yes to
it but it's enough that if somebody's
not really serious they're not even
going to pay attention to it and that's
why I like the $7 to $17 price point so
much on delivering value maybe I'll I'll
put like a mini course out there like a
like a three module like micro course
that's an introductory to people on what
to take and then the goal of that is to
move people along a path to where
they're able to see the
value and they're able to make a
decision that says okay I like Jeremiah
he's awesome I want to work with him
further and jump into his his program
and that's where then people can can try
out our program can can test drive it
can see under the hood as far as the
value that we deliver how it's how it's
truly better than anything else that's
out there that's delivered by other
people and again I'd love to I'd love to
work with you through that I'd love to
show you some of that as well inside of
our program uh if you if you're able to
jump into that I I truly truly believe
that it's one of the best programs on
the planet for this type of stuff okay
so when you're pricing your stuff out
anything that's under $97 is for
marketing purposes it's for building
that trust with people okay also
depending on what you're selling on the
back end if I was selling something for
maybe $20,000 as my main product I might
charge a little bit more like $200 or
$300 as the entry
level as far as that goes okay but you
don't you're not going to make a profit
on some on $97 sessions on on $200
sessions your profit margins are going
to come on things that are over $500
$1,000 and up and when you can truly
deliver value to people if you're
delivering at least $5,000 worth of
value to people they'll pay you 500
bucks if you're delivering at least
$10,000 worth of value to people they'll
pay you $1,000 cuz they're paying you $1
and getting 10 back in value and it's
and it really is a small fee for what
they're really getting on the back end
of that and so when you can work on a
how you think about yourself the value
that you're delivering to people and
you're no longer caught up in
the oh am I am I worth it you know is
this am I doing the right
thing am I are people going to actually
see my value are they actually going to
pay this for me and you start to say you
know what I believe in what I'm worth
and I believe in what my time is worth
and I'm worth it for the right people to
come in
not just anybody to work with me you can
start to position yourself as that
authority to the right people who will
start to recognize and see your value
and then they will start to come in and
they'll be like wow they'll see the
difference of working with you because
they will be served at such a high level
one of the best ways again to do this is
you can create pieces of content you can
create lowcost offers that that are not
intended for profit margin but for
building Trust trust and nurturing that
relationship and then you can make calls
to action to higher priced offers things
that are 500,000 2,000 10,000
$20,000 and by the way I believe anybody
watching this right now you can sell you
can package an offer of your services
that's worth $20,000 you might be saying
gosh what could I package for $20,000 I
had I had a health coach once who we
helped her with this it included like a
Year's worth of Health coaching uh lab
testing all the supplements things like
that sure yes did it cost her a couple
Grand per client to deliver some of that
it did there was a little bit of some
give and take on that but she was able
to price it in such a way that her
margins were so significant that her
business her name is Dawn she was able
to make over $35,000 a month by working
with us and putting this together and
really structuring an offer that people
really really want really loved and and
really
enjoyed doing and finding so the way
that we find our clients is through
content social media organic as well as
paid advertising we are able to use the
algorithms to our advantage to draw
people in and that's what I work with
people through in my coaching program to
know what is the right topics to talk
about what's the right messaging how do
we sell it how do we promote it how do
we put it all together so that they can
start to have consistent profits Clarity
in what they're doing and they know
exactly what the right things to do are
and the WR words to say to close the
sale and that starts to create the real
Financial Freedom and time freedom in
their life cuz I don't want to see you
burnt out I don't want to see you
working more than 10 to 15 hours a week
and I know that if you can really start
to apply yourself with this stuff and
you actually start to go to work and you
actually work with somebody like myself
to produce those results you'll start to
get them so listen I'd love to see you
in my program I'd love to work with you
subscribe to this channel keep watching
all the different videos that we put out
there I promise you we will serve you at
the highest level here on this YouTube
channel as well as on my Instagram and
Facebook you can go check those out as
well we'll talk soon have a good one
everybody